<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Srini&#39;s blog</title>
    <link>https://srinivasreddy.dev/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Srini&#39;s blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 17:02:12 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://srinivasreddy.dev/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Setup tailwindcss 2.0.1 for your projects</title>
      <link>https://srinivasreddy.dev/posts/tailwindcss-helloworld-2.0.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 17:02:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://srinivasreddy.dev/posts/tailwindcss-helloworld-2.0.1/</guid>
      <description>In this tutorial, I will explain the setup for tailwindcss 2.0.1. I found the official documentation is hard to follow and Adam&amp;rsquo;s YouTube video kind of outdated.
First, create a directory with your project name, here I created a project named tailwind-helloworld.
mkdir tailwind-helloworld Run the npm command - npm init -y to create a package.json with defaults.
Install tailwindcss and deps with the command npm install tailwindcss postcss autoprefixer postcss-cli</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Build companies logos as a service startup</title>
      <link>https://srinivasreddy.dev/posts/create-your-own-companies-logos-as-service-startup/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Nov 2020 17:07:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://srinivasreddy.dev/posts/create-your-own-companies-logos-as-service-startup/</guid>
      <description>While working on a project, I have to write a program to crawl logo images of various companies. I have automated this with puppeteer script written in Typescript/Javascript. While this script has done the job for me - extracting 100 odd companies logos, I have to warn you that I haven&amp;rsquo;t tested more than that.
You can install the required packages with the following commands,
npm i puppeteer puppeteer-extra-plugin-stealth --save npm i reflect-metadata node-fetch fs puppeteer-extra --save Then,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The best podcasts I listened</title>
      <link>https://srinivasreddy.dev/posts/best-podcasts-i-listened/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 16:28:15 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://srinivasreddy.dev/posts/best-podcasts-i-listened/</guid>
      <description>This post is an archive of the podcasts I have liked for the sheer brilliance of the interviewee.
This post will be updated as I listen more.
Note: The order of appearance does not indicate any preference.
  Machine Learning Joins with Arun Kumar
  Cruise: Self-Driving Engineering with Mo Elshenawy
  Kubernetes Vision with Joe Beda
  Envoy, with Matt Klein
  Future of Computing with John Hennessy Holiday Repeat</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Python crontab correctly</title>
      <link>https://srinivasreddy.dev/posts/using-python-crontab-correctly/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 11:46:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://srinivasreddy.dev/posts/using-python-crontab-correctly/</guid>
      <description>In this post, we are going to examine how to setup python-crontab correctly and debugging for possible errors and how to resolve them.
For the uninitiated, python-crontab is a python package for editing cron table aka crontab used for scheduling the jobs run by cron.
I have setup a cron job which runs for every hour. I have a file every_hour.py that contains the following code and sets up crontable entry to run cron.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://srinivasreddy.dev/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://srinivasreddy.dev/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi, Welcome to my site. I am a Software consultant and open-source developer living in Pune, India. In this website you may find articles about Python, rust and some other stuff.
The list of projects I have contributed to:
 Django Ipython Pytest CPython - (Python programming language). Rust - Programming language. MongoMock - In-memory mocking library for MongoDB with a minimal feature set. Cargo - Rust package manager. Pandas - Python data manipulation library.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comments Policy</title>
      <link>https://srinivasreddy.dev/comments-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://srinivasreddy.dev/comments-policy/</guid>
      <description>Comments are welcomed and encouraged on this site, but there are some instances where comments will be edited or deleted as follows:
1.Comments deemed to be spam or solely promotional in nature will be deleted. Including a link to relevant content is permitted, but comments should be relevant to the post topic.
2.Comments including profanity will be deleted.
3.Comments containing language or concepts that could be deemed offensive will be deleted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://srinivasreddy.dev/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://srinivasreddy.dev/contact/</guid>
      <description>You can contact me at thatiparthysreenivas@gmail.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hire Me</title>
      <link>https://srinivasreddy.dev/hireme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://srinivasreddy.dev/hireme/</guid>
      <description>You can hire me for your python/Django projects. Or as a python/rust engineer. I can write production-ready code in both Python and Rust.
I have experience with designing automation frameworks too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://srinivasreddy.dev/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://srinivasreddy.dev/projects/</guid>
      <description>allhub - Allhub is a client to connect to Github REST API v3.
soduku - Sudoku solver in Python - 2010ish
euler - Project Euler solutions
rust-bloomfilter - Bloom filter written in rust
companies-list - Fortune 1000 companies details scraped from fortune website. Written in Typescript using puppeteer library.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
